Guide to the George W. Wilbur Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile Material, 2.7; (6 boxes)
  - Box 67, folders 1276, 1286 (Box 114, Folder 1921)
  - Box 68, folders 1298, 1304-1305, 1307-1325 (Box 115, Folder 1922-1941)
  - Box 69, folders 1326-1343, 1345, 1350-1351, 1353-1354, 1356-1357 (Box 116, Folder 1942-1968)
  - Box 70, folders 1358-1370 (Box 116, Folder 1969-1977)
  - Box 71, folders 1378, 1382-1384 (Box 116, Folder 1978)
  - Box 72, folders 1386-1387 (Box 116, Folder 1979)
  - Box 88, folder 1538 (Box 117, Folder 1980)
  - Box 91, folders 1559, 1564-1566, 1568 (Box 118, Folder 1981-1983)
  - Box 92, folders 1573, 1575-1576, 1578-1579, 1583, 1588-1590, 1592 (Box 118, Folder 1984-1990)
  - Box 93, folders 1590, 1592, 1594-1595, 1599-1606, 1607-1609 (Box 118, Folder 1991-2005)
  - Box 99, folder 1726 (Box bsd, folder 2007)
  - Box 103, folder 1767 (Box 118, Folder 2005a)
  - Box 106, folder 1778 (Box 118, Folder 2006)